Guide to the Allen G. Kukovich Papers, 1977-2004 AIS.2004.21
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Other Initiatives and Organizational Involvements, 1981-2004; XI.
  - Marital Rape Bills, 1981-1988 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Abortion Control Bill, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Vietnam Veterans' Memorial Commission Bill, 1987-1989 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Township Treasurer Compensation Bill, 1987-1991 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Loan Interest and Protection Bill, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - County Sales Tax Bill, 1990-1991 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - National Library Week Bill, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - County Boundary Bill, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - SERVIS Program Information, 1995-1999 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - SERVIS Correspondence, 1997-2001 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - SERVIS Clippings, 1994-2003 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Police Loan Program Bill, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Homestead Exemption Tax, 1997-1999 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Uniform Construction Code Bill, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Gambling Bill, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Backend Referendum Bill, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 43)
- Audio/Visual Materials, XII.
  Series XII contains VHS, Beta, and 8mm videotapes; audio cassettes and compact discs; and data compact discs. These materials contain campaign advertisements, television appearances, radio talk shows, debates, materials on research subjects, and materials from constituents.
  - Audio/Visual Materials (Box 18-22)